{
	"en": "<HTML><BODY bgcolor=#CCE5F2><font face=\"Helvetica\"><B><font size=4 color=#0C2159><center>HELP</center></font></B><BR><font size=2 color=#000000><BR><B>Q:  How am I charged for something I purchase within the game (In-App Commerce / microtransaction)?<BR></B>A:  You are billed/charged the same way for any other purchase on your iPhone/iPod; through your iTunes account. If you have any billing disputes or questions, please contact Apple.<BR><BR><B>Q:  I purchased something in-game, but I cannot see it. What happened?<BR></B>A:  In some cases, you may need to exit the game and restart it to access your new content. If that doesn't work, try turning off your device and restarting it. You can always check what you've purchased by entering the game's portal (for example: for Sims 3, select 'The Sims Store' from the game's main menu, then select the 'My Stuff' folder in the lower left hand corner of the screen).<BR><BR><B>Q: I purchased something on my iPhone. Can I get this same content on my iPod (or vice-versa)?<BR></B>A: Yes, as long as those devices share the same iTunes account. First, start the game on the device you want the new content on (if you don't have the game on that device yet, enter the iTunes store and download it). Then, enter the game's portal (for example: for Sims 3, select 'The Sims Store' from the game's main menu, then select 'Restore Purchases' in the upper right hand corner of the screen). You can always check what you've purchased by selecting the 'My Stuff' folder in the lower left hand corner of the screen.<BR><BR><B>Q: My question is not answered here. What can I do?<BR></B>A: You can visit the FAQ sections at <a href=\"http://www.apple.com/support/itunes/store/games/\">http://www.apple.com/support/itunes/store/games/</a> and contact Apple for any billing issues, or visit <a href=\"http://support.eamobile.com\">http://support.eamobile.com<a> and write us. When contacting us, please include as much specific information as possible so that we can better assist you.<BR><BR><B>Q: What is your Privacy Policy?<BR></B>A: You can view EA's privacy policy by visiting <a href=\"http://www.ea.com/custom/privacy-policy\">http://www.ea.com/custom/privacy-policy</a>.<BR></font></font></BODY></HTML>",
	"fr": "<HTML><BODY bgcolor=#CCE5F2><font face=\"Helvetica\"><B><font size=4 color=#0C2159><center>FAQ Paiement iPhone/iPod</center></font></B><BR><font size=2 color=#000000><BR><B>Q : Comment se déroule le paiement des contenus que j’achète dans un jeu (In-App Commerce / micro-transaction) ?<BR></B>R : Le paiement s’effectue de la même façon que pour tout autre achat sur votre iPhone/iPod, c’est-à-dire par l’intermédiaire de votre compte iTunes. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes de paiement, ou si vous avez des questions, veuillez contacter Apple.<BR><BR><B>Q : J’ai acheté du contenu dans un jeu, mais je ne le trouve nulle part. Que se passe-t-il ?<BR></B>R : Dans certains cas, vous devez quitter le jeu et le redémarrer pour accéder au nouveau contenu. Si cela ne fonctionne pas, essayez d’éteindre votre appareil, puis de le rallumer. Vous pouvez également vérifier vos achats en accédant au portail du jeu (par exemple : pour Les Sims 3, sélectionnez « La Boutique Sims » depuis le menu principal du jeu, puis sélectionnez le dossier « Mon Équipement » dans le coin inférieur gauche de l’écran).<BR><BR><B>Q : J’ai acheté du contenu sur mon iPhone. Puis-je y accéder sur mon iPod (ou vice versa) ?<BR></B>R : Oui, si ces appareils partagent le même compte iTunes. Tout d’abord, démarrez le jeu sur l’appareil sur lequel vous souhaitez obtenir votre nouveau contenu (si vous ne possédez pas encore le jeu sur cet appareil, accédez à l’iTunes Store et téléchargez-le). Puis accédez au portail du jeu (par exemple : pour Les Sims 3, sélectionnez « La Boutique Sims » depuis le menu principal du jeu, puis sélectionnez « Rétablir achats » dans le coin supérieur droit de l’écran). Vous pouvez aussi vérifier vos achats en sélectionnant le dossier « Mon Équipement » dans le coin inférieur gauche de l’écran.<BR><BR><B>Q : Je ne trouve pas la réponse à ma question dans cette FAQ. Que dois-je faire ?<BR></B>R : Consultez les sections FAQ sur <a href=\"http://www.apple.com/support/itunes/store/games/\">http://www.apple.com/support/itunes/store/games/</a> et contactez Apple pour tout problème de paiement, ou rendez-vous sur <a href=\"http://support.eamobile.com\">http://support.eamobile.com</a> (site en anglais) pour nous écrire. Si vous nous contactez, assurez-vous de nous fournir le maximum d’informations dont vous disposez afin que nous puissions vous aider du mieux possible.<BR><BR><B>Q : Pouvez-vous m’en dire plus sur votre Charte de confidentialité ?<BR></B>R : Vous pouvez consulter la Charte de confidentialité d’EA en vous rendant sur <a href=\"http://www.ea.com/custom/privacy-policy\">http://www.ea.com/custom/privacy-policy</a><BR></font></font></BODY></HTML>",
	"it": "<HTML><BODY bgcolor=#CCE5F2><font face=\"Helvetica\"><B><font size=4 color=#0C2159><center>FAQ fatturazione iPhone/iPod</center></font></B><BR><font size=2 color=#000000><BR><B>Q: Come vengono addebitati gli acquisti di prodotti effettuati all'interno del gioco (In-App Commerce / microtransazioni)?<BR></B>A: La procedura di addebito è la medesima di qualsiasi altro prodotto acquistato su iPhone o iPod, ovvero avviene tramite il tuo account iTunes. Per domande o problemi relativi ai pagamenti, contatta Apple.<BR><BR><B>Q: Ho acquistato un prodotto all'interno del gioco, ma non riesco a trovarlo. Perché?<BR></B>A: In alcuni casi potrebbe essere necessario uscire dal gioco e riavviarlo per accedere a un nuovo contenuto. Se ciò non dovesse bastare, prova a spegnere e riaccendere il dispositivo. Per verificare gli acquisti effettuati, puoi accedere al portale del gioco (ad esempio: per The Sims 3, seleziona \"The Sims Store\" dal menu principale del gioco e quindi la cartella \"I miei oggetti\" nell’angolo in basso a sinistra della schermata).<BR><BR><B>Q: Ho acquistato un contenuto su iPhone. Posso usufruirne anche su iPod (e viceversa)?<BR></B>A: Sì, ma i due dispositivi devono condividere il medesimo account iTunes. Per prima cosa, avvia il gioco sul dispositivo in cui intendi usufruire del nuovo contenuto (se non hai ancora installato il gioco su quel dispositivo, vai al negozio online iTunes e scaricalo). A questo punto accedi al portale del gioco (ad esempio: per The Sims 3, seleziona \"The Sims Store\" dal menu principale del gioco e quindi \"Ripristina acquisti\" nell’angolo in alto a destra della schermata). Per verificare gli acquisti effettuati, puoi selezionare la cartella \"I miei oggetti\" nell’angolo in basso a sinistra della schermata.<BR><BR><B>Q: Qui non trovo risposte alle mie domande. Cosa posso fare?<BR></B>A: Puoi visitare la sezione FAQ del sito <a href=\"http://www.apple.com/support/itunes/store/games/\">http://www.apple.com/support/itunes/store/games/</a> e contattare Apple per i problemi relativi ai pagamenti; oppure visitare il sito  <a href=\"http://support.eamobile.com\">http://support.eamobile.com</a> e scriverci. Ti preghiamo di fornire più dettagli possibile in merito al tuo problema; questo ci consentirà di assisterti al meglio.<BR><BR><B>Q: Che tipo di Politica sulla privacy applicate?<BR></B>A: Puoi visionare la politica sulla privacy di EA all'indirizzo <a href=\"http://www.ea.com/custom/privacy-policy\">http://www.ea.com/custom/privacy-policy</a>. <BR></font></font></BODY></HTML>",
	"de": "<HTML><BODY bgcolor=#CCE5F2><font face=\"Helvetica\"><B><font size=4 color=#0C2159><center>FAQs zur Bezahlung bei iPhone/iPod</center></font></B><BR><font size=2 color=#000000><BR><B>F: Wie bezahle ich für etwas, das ich im Spiel kaufe (In App Commerce/Mikrotransaktion)?<BR></B>A: Das wird genau wie bei allen anderen Einkäufen auf deinem iPhone/iPod auch über dein iTunes-Konto abgerechnet. Solltest du noch Fragen zur Bezahlung haben, kontaktiere bitte Apple.<BR><BR><B>F: Ich habe im Spiel etwas gekauft, aber ich finde es nicht. Was ist geschehen?<BR></B>A: Es kann sein, dass du das Spiel verlassen und neu starten musst, um deinen neuen Inhalt aufzurufen. Wenn das nicht funktioniert, schalte dein Gerät aus und starte es erneut. Du kannst deine Einkäufe jederzeit im Portal des Spiels ansehen (für Die Sims 3 wählst du zum Beispiel das Sims Store aus dem Hauptmenü des Spiels und dann den Ordner ‘Meine Sachen’ in der linken unteren Ecke des Bildschirms).<BR><BR><B>F: Ich habe auf meinem iPhone etwas gekauft. Kann ich den Inhalt auch auf meinem iPod nutzen (und umgekehrt)?<BR></B>A: Ja, so lange du für beide Geräte dasselbe iTunes-Konto hast. Starte zuerst das Spiel auf dem Gerät, auf dem du den neuen Inhalt haben möchtest (falls du das Spiel auf dem entsprechenden Gerät noch nicht hast, geh zum iTunes Store und lade es herunter). Rufe dann das Portal des Spiels auf (für Die Sims 3 wählst du zum Beispiel das Sims Store aus dem Hauptmenü des Spiels und dann ‘Einkäufe wiederherstellen’ in der rechten oberen Ecke des Bildschirms). Du kannst deine Einkäufe jederzeit ansehen, wenn du den Ordner ‘Meine Sachen’ in der linken unteren Ecke des Bildschirms auswählst.<BR><BR><B>F: Keine der Antworten passt zu meiner Frage. Was kann ich jetzt machen?<BR></B>A: Du kannst dir die FAQs auf <a href=\"http://www.apple.com/support/itunes/store/games/\">http://www.apple.com/support/itunes/store/games/</a> ansehen und bei Fragen zur Bezahlung Apple kontaktieren. Oder du besuchst <a href=\"http://support.eamobile.com\">http://support.eamobile.com</a> und schreibst uns. Sende uns bitte so viele detaillierte Informationen wie möglich, damit wir deine Frage besser beantworten können.<BR><BR><B>F: Wie lautet die Datenschutzrichtlinie?<BR></B>A: Du kannst dir die Datenschutzrichtlinie von EA auf <a href=\"http://www.ea.com/custom/privacy-policy\">http://www.ea.com/custom/privacy-policy</a> ansehen.<BR></font></font></BODY></HTML>",
	"es": "<HTML><BODY bgcolor=#CCE5F2><font face=\"Helvetica\"><B><font size=4 color=#0C2159><center>Preguntas frecuentes sobre la facturación de iPhone/iPod</center></font></B><BR><font size=2 color=#000000><BR><B>P: ¿Cómo pago por algo que compro dentro del juego (compra de aplicaciones internas o microtransacciones)?<BR></B>R: Se te facturará o cobrará como cuando realizas cualquier otra compra desde tu iPhone/iPod a través de tu cuenta iTunes. Si tienes problemas o dudas sobre la facturación, ponte en contacto con Apple.<BR><BR><B>P: He comprado algo dentro del juego pero no consigo verlo. ¿Qué ocurre?<BR></B>R: En algunos casos, necesitarás salir del juego y reiniciarlo para acceder al contenido nuevo. Si no funciona, intenta apagar el dispositivo y reiniciarlo. Si entras en la página inicial del juego puedes visualizar las compras que has realizado (por ejemplo: en Los Sims 3, seleccionas \"Tiendo Los Sims\" del menú principal y, después, seleccionas la carpeta \"Mis cosas\", situada en la esquina inferior izquierda de la pantalla).<BR><BR><B>P: He comprado desde el iPhone. ¿Puedo colocar el mismo contenido en mi iPod (o viceversa)?<BR></B>R: Sí, siempre que los dispositivos compartan la misma cuenta iTunes. Primero, inicia el juego en el dispositivo en el que quieras incluir el contenido nuevo (si aún no tienes el juego en ese dispositivo, entra en iTunes Store y descárgatelo). Después, entra en la página inicial del juego (por ejemplo: en Los Sims 3, selecciona \"Tienda los Sims\" del menú principal y, después, selecciona \"Recuperar compras\", situado en la esquina superior derecha de la pantalla). Si seleccionas la carpeta \"Mis cosas\", situada en la esquina inferior izquierda de la pantalla, podrás visualizar las compras que has realizado.<BR><BR><B>P: Mis dudas no se resuelven con estas preguntas. ¿Qué puedo hacer?<BR></B>R: Puedes visitar la sección de preguntas frecuentes en <a href=\"http://www.apple.com/support/itunes/store/games/\">http://www.apple.com/support/itunes/store/games/</a> y ponerte en contacto con Apple para cualquier problema con la facturación, o visitar <a href=\"http://support.eamobile.com\">http://support.eamobile.com</a> y escribirnos. Cuando te pongas en contacto con nosotros, incluye toda la información posible para poder ofrecerte la mejor asistencia.<BR><BR><B>P: What is your Privacy Policy?<BR></B>R: Visita <a href=\"http://www.ea.com/custom/privacy-policy\">http://www.ea.com/custom/privacy-policy</a> para acceder a la política de privacidad de EA. <BR></font></font></BODY></HTML>",
	"ja": "<HTML><BODY bgcolor=#CCE5F2><font face=\"Helvetica\"><B><font size=4 color=#0C2159><center>よくある質問：iPhone／iPodの請求処理について</center></font></B><BR><font size=2 color=#000000><BR><B>Q:  ゲーム中で購入したもの（ゲーム内商品／小額決済）に対して、どのように請求されるのでしょうか？<BR></B>A:  お使いのiPhone／iPodでの他の取引と同様に、お使いのiTunesアカウントを通じて請求／課金されます。請求に関するお問い合わせやご質問は、Apple社にご連絡ください。<BR><BR><B>Q:  ゲーム内で購入したはずのものが表示されませんが、なぜでしょうか？<BR></B>A: 場合によっては、新しいコンテンツを利用するにはゲームをいったん終了して再起動する必要があります。それでもうまくいかない場合、デバイスの電源をいったん切ったうえで入れなおしてみてください。なお、ゲームのポータルにアクセスすれば購入内容をご確認いただけます（例えば「ザ・シムズ3」であれば、ゲームのメインメニューから「The Sims ストア」を選択して、画面左下に表示される「マイ スタッフ」フォルダを選択してください）。<BR><BR><B>Q: iPhoneで購入したコンテンツ を、iPodで利用することは可能でしょうか？（また、その逆は可能でしょうか？）<BR></B>A: 両方のデバイスで同一のiTunesアカウントを使用している限り、可能です。まずは新しいコンテンツを利用したいデバイスでゲームを起動してください（そのデバイスにまだゲームがインストールされていない場合、iTunesストアからダウンロードしてください）。次にゲームのポータルにアクセスしてください（例えば「ザ・シムズ3」であれば、ゲームのメインメニューから「ザ・シムズ ストア 」を選択して、画面右上に表示される「購入内容の再適用 」を選択してください）。なお、画面左下に表示される「マイ スタッフ 」フォルダを選択すれば 、いつでも購入したものをご確認いただけます。<BR><BR><B>Q: ここでは質問の答えが見つからなかったのですが、どうすればいいでしょうか？<BR></B>A: <a href=\"http://www.apple.com/support/itunes/store/games/\">http://www.apple.com/support/itunes/store/games/</a>のよくある質問コーナーにアクセスしてください。課金についてはそこからApple社にお問い合わせいただくか、<a href=\"http://support.eamobile.com\">http://support.eamobile.com</a> から弊社にお問い合わせください。ご連絡をいただく際は、より適切な対応を可能にするため、できる限り具体的な情報を含めていただけるよう、お願い申し上げます。<BR><BR><B>Q: プライバシーに関する方針を確認したいのですが？<BR></B>A: エレクトロニックアーツのプライバシーに関する方針は <a href=\"http://www.ea.com/custom/privacy-policy\">http://www.ea.com/custom/privacy-policy</a> からご確認いただけます。 <BR></font></font></BODY></HTML>",
	"zh": "<HTML><BODY bgcolor=#CCE5F2><font face=\"Helvetica\"><B><font size=4 color=#0C2159><center>帮助</center></font></B><BR><font size=2 color=#000000><BR><B>问题：在游戏中购买物品后（程序内嵌商务或零售）如何付款？<BR></B>答案：类似于在 iPhone/iPod 上购买其他物品，你可以通过 iTunes 账号支付或被收取费用。如果你有任何付款纠纷或问题，请联系 Apple。<BR><BR><B>问题：我在游戏中购买了一件物品，但是看不到它。怎么回事？<BR></B>答案：有时候，你需要退出并重新启动游戏才能获得新物品。如果这不起作用，尝试关闭设备并重启。你总是可以通过进入游戏启动画面来查看已购买的商品（例如：在《模拟人生3》中，你可以首先选择主菜单中的「Sims商店」，然后选择画面左下角的「我的物品」文件夹）。<BR><BR><B>问题：我使用 iPhone 购买了一件物品。我在 iPod 中也可以拥有它吗（反之亦然）？<BR></B>答案A: 是的，只要那些设备都共用一个 iTunes 账号。首先，在你希望获取新物品的设备上运行游戏（如果这台设备还没有这款游戏，请登录 iTunes 商店下载它）。然后进入游戏启动画面（例如：在《模拟人生3》中，你可以首先选择主菜单中的「Sims商店」，然后选择画面右上角的「恢复购买」）。<BR><BR><B>问题：这里没有我所需要的答案。我该怎么做？<BR></B>答案：你可以访问 <a href=\"http://www.apple.com/support/itunes/store/games/\">http://www.apple.com/support/itunes/store/games/</a> 的疑难解答部分并联系 Apple 解决任何付款问题，或访问 <a href=\"http://support.eamobile.com\">http://support.eamobile.com</a> 致函我们。请在信中尽可能地详述信息，以便我们更好地为你服务。<BR><BR><B>问题：隐私政策的内容？<BR></B>答案：你可以访问 <a href=\"http://www.ea.com/custom/privacy-policy\">http://www.ea.com/custom/privacy-policy</a> 查询 EA 隐私政策。<BR></font></font></BODY></HTML>",
	"ko": "<HTML><BODY bgcolor=#CCE5F2><font face=\"Helvetica\"><B><font size=4 color=#0C2159><center>HELP</center></font></B><BR><font size=2 color=#000000><BR><B>Q: 게임에서 구매한 상품에 대한 요금 지불은 어떻게 진행되나요?<BR></B>A: 아이폰이나 아이팟에서 다른 상품을 구입했을때와 같은 방법으로 요금이 지불됩니다. 요금 지불에 대해 궁금한 점이 있으면 애플사로 연락주시기 바랍니다. <BR><BR><B>Q: 게임에서 구매한 상품이 보이지 않습니다. 어떻게 된건가요?<BR></B>A: 새로 구매한 컨텐츠를 확인하려면 게임을 종료하고 다시 시작해야되는 경우도 있습니다. 그래도 보이지 않는다면 전원을 껐다가 다시 시작해 보십시오. 언제든지 게임 메뉴에서 자신이 구매한 상품을 확인할 수 있습니다.(예를 들어, 심즈 3에서는 메인 메뉴의 '심즈 스토어'를 선택하고 화면 왼쪽 아래의 ''내 아이템 폴더를 선택하면 됩니다.)<BR><BR><B>Q: 아이폰으로 구매한 상품을 아이팟에서 받아볼 수 있나요?(또는 반대 상황)<BR></B>A: 네, 두개의 장치가 같은 아이튠즈 계정을 사용한다면 가능합니다. 먼저 상품을 사용할 장치에서 게임을 시작합니다. (장치에 게임이 없으면 아이튠즈 스토어에서 게임을 다운로드 받으십시오.) 게임 메뉴로 들어갑니다. (예를 들어, 심즈 3에서는 메인 메뉴의 '심즈 스토어'를 선택하고 화면 오른쪽 위의 '구매 항목 불러오기'를 선택합니다.)<BR><BR><B>Q: 원하는 질문이 여기에 없습니다. 어떻게 해야 하나요?<BR></B>A:애플사의 <a href=\"http://www.apple.com/support/itunes/store/games/\">http://www.apple.com/support/itunes/store/games/</a> FAQ 메뉴에 요금과 관련된 질문을 올리시거나, 저희 웹사이트 <a href=\"http://support.eamobile.com\">http://support.eamobile.com<a>에 글을 남겨 주시기 바랍니다. 글을 남기실 때에는 저희가 최대한의 지원을 할 수 있도록 가능하면 자세한 모든 정보를 포함해 주시기 바라니다.<BR><BR><B>Q: 귀사의 개인 정보 보호 정책은 어떻게 되나요?<BR></B>A: <a href=\"http://www.ea.com/custom/privacy-policy\">http://www.ea.com/custom/privacy-policy</a>에서 EA의 개인 정보 보호 정책을 확인할 수 있습니다.<BR></font></font></BODY></HTML>"
}
